Kostadis Roussos: I'm okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, righty.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go…
Kostadis Roussos: I do not want that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you are still in the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: But she step out the tavern. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: As you step out of the tavern.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, as you step… okay, so we step out of the… I'm gonna send him to the changelayer…
Kostadis Roussos: You step out of the tavern. Where do you want to go? To Barthin's prov… as you step… sorry, as you step out of the tavern,
Kostadis Roussos: The guy that you guys were… was following you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I was following him.
Kostadis Roussos: You're following him, right? Yes. So, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So… I presume you're trying to be discreet?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I can roll the stealth.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Roll list it?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll, roll as you roll.
Kostadis Roussos: 4 plus 7, 11.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: So… As you get to over about here…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Maybe.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice… just make sure I got this right…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Another person?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Aye.
Kostadis Roussos: That's not the right one.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go. That's what I'm supposed to use.
Kostadis Roussos: Get some of the guys some excuse.
Kostadis Roussos: You realize that there's 4 guys, and they're kind of… Holding an ambush.
Kostadis Roussos: Shit.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? That you, you, you notice them, just rather roll your perception.
Kostadis Roussos: Exception.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, Insight Investigation, insider investigation, sorry, Insider Investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, okay, so, not a perception. Bad role, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: No, don't… ignore that. Roll your investigation.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Investigations.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Stood by.
Kostadis Roussos: No, that's 23, man. That's very good. Yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I thought it was a 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it was about to be a 1.
Kostadis Roussos: 1 and 19 are on opposite sides.
Kostadis Roussos: No, 1 and 20 are on opposite sides, sorry. Alright, so, you see that there are four, there are four of these guys who are, sort of.
Kostadis Roussos: As you turn around the corner, you realize that there are 4 of them.
Kostadis Roussos: And the guy you were following… Is kinda just standing there.
Kostadis Roussos: And… looking around to see where you are.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, the rest of you, I presume, are sort of over here.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay, so…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: the car.
Kostadis Roussos: But…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right around the corner.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, right around the corner, so I'm assuming you're right around the corner. Alright, so Xenovan, do you want to, shout and tell your friends to attack? Do you want to go back? Like, they're obviously out to gang up on you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'm gonna call my friends for help.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you wanna call… do you wanna… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: But I…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I need to, like, if they're not ready to engage, I'm gonna have to talk to them, like, who are you guys? Oh, that sounds like a good ambush.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, they clearly are looking to ambush you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Are they not gonna engage talking with me?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, so, so it's… so…
Kostadis Roussos: You could always, like, you know, Bravely and spectacularly say, Can't we just talk?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Well…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, this is, this is my response.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, I'm just gonna say, you can do that. He's the, like…
Kostadis Roussos: This guy sort of, like, is waiting for… to see if, like, the one guy who is… you were, who you were following is sort of waiting for you guys to… to follow… looks like he's looking for you guys to follow, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And he's kind of getting disappointed.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, okay, so when I noticed the ambush, I'm gonna ask him, so, looks like you were expecting me, like, are you not gonna introduce me to your friends?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, so that's your routine, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, that's my response, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: However, before you do that, roll an intimidation check.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Intimidations? Okay, interesting. Never done those.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I think it's the 19th.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see what happens.
Kostadis Roussos: Sweet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Is it to see that I'm intimidated, or the other person is.
Kostadis Roussos: No, did you intimidate him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Perfect.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just do something…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So were we.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you tried to intimidate him.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh wait, would you try to intimidate him?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, I got a 20…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 19… no, I got 19…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… He causes him to pause you for a second, he wasn't expecting you to… do that.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: So, he's kind of like, he's got this look where he's trying to sense your motives, see what your plans are.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, he's gonna see, wait for my plan to roll?
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, yeah, you kind of, like, he's not… he's paused, he wasn't expecting you to do that, so now… so now he's kind of like, okay…
Kostadis Roussos: What's your next move?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, I'll just tell them, let me bring some of my friends to introduce to you as well, and I'm gonna call them.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're gonna up the intimidation level.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Roll the implementation again, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you…
Kostadis Roussos: What did you get?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 1 and 13…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, if you're gonna introduce your friends, I'm gonna introduce MY friends! Get them, guys!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, it's gonna get messy. Fine.
Kostadis Roussos: It's gonna get messy.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Alright.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, roll for initiative.
Kostadis Roussos: They're, they're, they're a gang, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And as far as they've concerned, they were running this town, and you've shown up, and are now gonna tell them who they can and can't do anything to?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, so these are the red brats.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You could tell they're red brands because they've got red cloaks. Oh, I'm sorry, you didn't see the… sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you should… did you not see their names? No.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, there are no names.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, if I don't see names, just tell me, because I didn't notice that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, so there's Red Brand Ruffian, Red Brand Ruffian.
Kostadis Roussos: 2… 3…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? Yes, I see, yes. Alright, so they're very impressed with your balls.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: As they should be.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'll… It's gonna roll an initiative check.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna get a generic battle map.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 9, 14.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just gonna do something here.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: That's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let the… so the band… the bandits are sort of, like… Here.
Kostadis Roussos: You're sort of over here, and your guys are kind of over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Can I move these characters a little bit?
Kostadis Roussos: Which ones? Yours? Yeah, you should be able to.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So… I'm thinking somewhere like this, and this guy… this guy was, like, 3 squares, I had 3 or 4 squares, because we were talking.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so he's right over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, I see one guy in corner, that is fine.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you saw all 4 of them, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct, yes, yes. All three of them are in each corner, which is perfect. Okay, cool. Yeah, this is, this is more like it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, roll for… why don't you roll for initiative?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I did, I got a 14.
Kostadis Roussos: You got a 14?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, 14.
Kostadis Roussos: I've got a 20, 20… About 19?
Kostadis Roussos: There, I've got the 8 plus 2.
Kostadis Roussos: 3… And this one… Plus 0, 14.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I forgot the question.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, this guy… Character sheet.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Only four, four in the turn order, or just the red one.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep. Yeah, there's only 4 red brands, yeah? Right.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do we get an initiative turning? Like…
Kostadis Roussos: So, we all rolled for initiatives. Do you see the turn order?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I see only the red brands in the turn order.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you guys, you should… you're there, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, no, that's what I'm saying.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that's… I see what the problem is, my bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I, I, yeah, no wonder you're confused.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Xenovan had a 14, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I had 14 years.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Sister Mela… Pip.
Kostadis Roussos: I had a 19?
Kostadis Roussos: Melavera had a 4.
Kostadis Roussos: And, we'll just give her a 10.
Kostadis Roussos: Since I can't be bothered to… Alright, now you should see yourselves, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, good. Alright, so everybody good now?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Here.
Kostadis Roussos: The red brand ruffins.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right, okay.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They look like Targaryens from Game of Thrones.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: They look like the Targaryens from the Game of Thrones, pictures with the blonde.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, yeah, they do, they don't that, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So,
Kostadis Roussos: No, he wouldn't do that. Alright, attacks Sister Mela with his short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: And does 4 points of damage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: What does PIP do?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming he's going to,
Kostadis Roussos: He's going to, attack… try to defend his… attack. Who do you want him to attack?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: The guy that's closer to him on the right side, like, on the bottom.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just give these guys numbers so that it's easier.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, which one? Do you want the one that says 1 or 2?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 2.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so Pip's gonna go over here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Probably a good, good decision. Alright, roll, alright, roll to attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do I roll?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, you roll, dude, I'm like…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Poor him.
Kostadis Roussos: You can either roll on… you can either roll dice if you have dice, if not, I will… I will get you some dice, because it always brings me joy to buy dice for players.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I don't have that. Wait, wait, hold on, I think I might have.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, dude, you just… or you can use the command line directly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, one sec, please.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have, I have this.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a… That's a DT, yeah.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: And I have this, that's a D…
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's a D10 as well.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: That's a detail note, and…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so just…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Ready.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, well, roll the 20.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll to hit.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 18?
Kostadis Roussos: That is a hit.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, you can use a hip.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, I will… you… the way… oh!
Kostadis Roussos: How much damage does he do?
Kostadis Roussos: He rolls a D8, so roll a D8. So the way you roll a D8 in… you can either go into D…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: These are the dies I have, so…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, but if you go, like, yeah, so to roll it electronically, you go into Roll20.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, R… Large date.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, D8.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Slash RD8, sorry, slash RD8.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. 4. Alright, so he also… but, he gets a strength bonus.
Kostadis Roussos: I know what it is, just hold on, I have to get it, I have to just,
Kostadis Roussos: His strength bonus is,
Kostadis Roussos: Plus 2, so he does 6 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Not bad.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: But then this other… this guy here goes, you arrogant… you think you're… you think you're so… tough, I'll show you what tough feels like.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And he, attacks you with a short sword.
Kostadis Roussos: And does 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, it's your turn.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I reduce my…
Kostadis Roussos: HP by 5.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, current night.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: No, I increased the damage to 5, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Your, your, yes, well, so it starts with your maximum, and you keep subtracting.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Correct, yeah, I mean, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Did you, did you mark it in your, your character sheet?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, so there are two ways. One is to…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you apply damage, and the others, you could do subtraction, yes, whatever, whatever works.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, yes, nothing. 5 points of damage.
Kostadis Roussos: Turns out, cognitively, dissubtraction is hard for humans. Alright, Xenobon, you're up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Now remember, you've got the NIC and the VEX option, right?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, Vex is, like, taking a… take a damage to it next attack goes against the creature.
Kostadis Roussos: So, so if you use Vex, your next attack can have a sneak attack bonus.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'll do the NIC.
Kostadis Roussos: The Nick doesn't, but you can run away without being attacked.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I'm gonna run away.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, probably the right decision. Alright, so roll an attack.
Kostadis Roussos: Thank you.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, B20, right? I'll just do this.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Fix the cash flow.
Kostadis Roussos: So you can gr- you can click on the, the, the…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Like, on the…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thank you, perfect.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This one, no, wait, I'm gonna use the dagger, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you first click on the daggers, so you see where… do you see all the way on the left? Here.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: This one, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Click that.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Do I have a disadvantage?
Kostadis Roussos: No, you don't have disadvantage. You only have disadvantage when you're in the dark. You don't have advantage. Does that make sense?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And that is a hit for 7 points of damage!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Thanks, cheers.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, do your second attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Second attack goes with.
Kostadis Roussos: Scimitar. Scimitar.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see… Alright, that's another 7 points of damage. Damn!
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: So, you must be bleeding.
Kostadis Roussos: The guy's, like, bleeding. Do you… and I presume you disengage and go towards your group?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, I run back.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Sister Mela… Is she…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: take on this guy, right? There's one guy in the corner who has…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he hasn't, he hasn't attacked yet. Sister Mela looks at, the red brand ruffian and says, I'll take care of him.
Kostadis Roussos: And she attempts to attack.
Kostadis Roussos: And she misses spectacularly. Alright, this red brand ruffian attacks Thistle.
Kostadis Roussos: Not thistle, pit.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Pip's Armor Clause?
Kostadis Roussos: Oops, armor class is… what is his armor class? 16.
Kostadis Roussos: That is a 15, that is a miss.
Kostadis Roussos: And then, this guy… Charges… Straight over there.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Now it's Vera's turn.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Nothing, kindly.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, Vera decides that, you know what, when in doubt, cast Magic Missile.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, see, it does… she kills this guy.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Oh, wow, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he only had 2 hit points left.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Drops this guy by 4…
Kostadis Roussos: And drops this guy by 4.
Kostadis Roussos: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: This red brand… Decides to attack Sister Mela again.
Kostadis Roussos: And he does 8 points of damage. She's hurting now.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let me just, she, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, okay. So, Pip, you're up. Pip's up. Roll for Pip's attack. Hold on. Before he does that, he's got a special ability.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you can't use it. Alright. Go for it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, I'm gonna do another time.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll a D20.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you hit! Alright, roll for damage. D… 8. Yep, D8 plus 2.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 3 points of time.
Kostadis Roussos: Not doing very well there, Pip.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 1 plus 2 is 3.
Kostadis Roussos: I think there's one more thing you can do, right? I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, alright, Xenovan, you're up.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Pip's up! Yeah, Xinavan, you're up.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so the, the, the guy who's… all of these guys can, can be used to,
Kostadis Roussos: You can have sneak attack bonus, so pick whoever you want.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Sneaked echo…
Kostadis Roussos: That gives, remember, 2D6 additional points of 2…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so this is where, if you use VEX…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, sir. Okay, so you attack with your scimitar first.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, with an advantage, or just.
Kostadis Roussos: Normal, no advantage.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Which is the left one, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And the result is…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Scimitar to hit, 19 scimitar, 4 scimitar, Sneak Attack, and 4.
Kostadis Roussos: So, 8 points of dem… oh, hold on.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, 8.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you're a first level, sorry, you're not second, you're not third level, right? So, 8 points of damage. Well done!
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, now you have advantage with your second attack.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Second attack, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Shift, and then plus, and…
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, oh yeah, I got a plus now, okay. I'll use the shorts for?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, with the… no, with the dagger.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Dang it.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Wait, why? Why cannot I use that?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, short swords, yeah, you could use the short sword, yeah, my bad. You couldn't use the short sword.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: incorrect.
Kostadis Roussos: 8.
Kostadis Roussos: 11 damage.
Kostadis Roussos: 11 damage?
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just see what this stupid meeting is.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I have a meeting now?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. I wanna see if I do.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: 9.30.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to go to this meeting.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay, okay, cool.
Kostadis Roussos: It was good hanging up, man.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yes, yes, we'll catch up tomorrow.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we will. This was, this was a little bit of a, little bit of a, A cliffhanger.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. Alright, take care. Take care, guys.
Nikhil Reddy Mettupally: I'll see you tomorrow, bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.